-> What is Kubernetes?
	Open source container orchestration tool
-> Developed by Google
-> What it does?
	It help you manage containerized application in deferent envirments

-> What are the main core components of Kubernetes?
	-Worker Node
	-Pod (the smallest part of kubernetese), Absteraction over container
	-Cluster-IP
	-Service:permanent IP address also is a load balancer
	-External service: a service is expose to out of K8s 
	-Ingress : recive the external request then forward to the services(routing traffic)
	-ConfigMap: contain the external configurations like appsettings
	-Secret: Like configMap keeps values in base64 encoded format
	-Volumes: attach an external storage to K8s
	-Cluster
	-Deployment:is a blueprint of your pod
	-StatefulSet: a consist place for keep the databases or any stateful applications
	-Kubelet: is responsible to install & run the containers runtime on the pod
	-Kube Proxy: manage the traffic route over the pods and services to minimize the data routing.
	-Master Node: Control the pod schedule, monitor the pod activity, re-start the pod, stop/start or increase the pod numbers
		-Api Server; Is a kind of Cluster gateway located in master component also acts as an authenticator
		-Scheduler:
		-Controller Manager: detect cluster state change(say to scheduler to add or remove a pod in a node)
		-etcd: this is the brain of master pod, keep all data the claster needs| is a key-value store
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
-> What is Minikube?
	Is an open source tools let you to run your solution on local machine. 
	It has 1 Master & Worker pod and pre-installed docker runtime inside of it.
	It runs on virtual machine.
	For testing purpose.
-> What is kubectl:
	Is a CLI to comunicate with kubernetes clusters.
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
-> What is the namespace in kubernetes?
	there is a way to organise resources in cluster.
	Is a kind of virtual cluster inside a cluster.
	there are 4 default namespace.
	Avoid override configs or apps when you work with 2 team.
	versioning the application.
	Handle the staging,prod, dev environment
	Limit access to cluster for specific team.
	Limit the resources like CPU, RAM, etc.

------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Commands:
kubectl create deployment nginx-depl --image=nginx
kubectl create namespace [name]